{
    "subject": "resource/Adolph_Strecker",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Darmstadt",
    "human_readable": "Adolph Strecker was born in Darmstadt.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8966188430786133,
            "question": "Name the city where Adolph Strecker was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8823456168174744,
            "question": "Where was Adolph Strecker born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.79254150390625,
            "question": "In what year was Adolph Strecker born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5062330961227417,
            "question": "What is Adolph Strecker known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41232359409332275,
            "question": "Is Adolph Strecker related to any famous figures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4071103036403656,
            "question": "Did Adolph Strecker travel extensively?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3919764459133148,
            "question": "What scientific field did Adolph Strecker contribute to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3658613860607147,
            "question": "What is one notable achievement of Adolph Strecker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3375818133354187,
            "question": "Where did Adolph Strecker likely receive his education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21048739552497864,
            "question": "What was the impact of Adolph Strecker's work on society?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adolph Strecker was born in Darmstadt.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7151_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Adolph Strecker likely receive his education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7151_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is one notable achievement of Adolph Strecker?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7151_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What scientific field did Adolph Strecker contribute to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7151_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7151_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7151_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7151_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7151_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7151_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7151_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7151_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7151_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7151_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7151_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Adolph Strecker was born in Darmstadt. This information can be found in multiple files, including `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7151/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt`, `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7151/re-ranker-msmarco/27.txt`."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Adolph Friedrich Ludwig Ewald Strecker was born on October 21, 1822, in Darmstadt, Germany."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}